

PERSONAL DATA

- NAME SZYMON MOZOL
- ADDRESS NYSA, MARIACKA 1B/3
- **PHONE NUMBER** +48 512 743 315
- **EMAIL** SZYMONMOZOL123@GMAIL.COM
- in LINKEDIN

WEBSITES



MYSITE



GITHUB



ITCH.IO



NEWGROUNDS



FIVERR



YOUTUBE

SKILLS

- C#
- UNITY ENGINE
- GIT
- CODE OPTIMIZATION
- DESIGN PRINCIPLES
- DESIGN PATTERNS
- ALGORITHMS AND DATA STRUCTURES

LANGUAGES

POLISH (NATIVE) ENGLISH (B2) GERMAN (A1)

SZYMON MOZOL

UNITY DEVELOPER/PROGRAMMER

I am a bachelor's degree holder in Computer Science at WSB Merito University in Wrocław with specialization in cloud application developer. I spend most of my time creating games in Unity Engine with emphasis on programming them. I am learning to program in C# but i also know Java and C++. I can write clean, optimal and efficient code. I know the Unity engine very well, I can use event system, animations, UI, particle system, lighting system, sound system, the new Input system, import assets and configure them, handle 2D/3D graphics and much more. Ever since my childhood, I have cultivated a deep fascination for video games. Creating, playing, immersing myself in discussions about them, and avidly watching gaming content are my primary passions.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Mar 2023 - currently

Junior Web Developer
Weni Solutions, Nysa

Jan 2023 - Apr 2023 Collins Aerospace, Wrocław

Jan 2022 - Apr 2022 Zara Poland, Wrocław

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021 Żabka Poland

Jan 2019 - Jun 2019

IT specialist
Specialist Hospital MSWiA in
Głuchołazy



EDUCATION

2020 - 2023 Bachelor degree WSB Merito University, Wrocław

2016-2020 Secondary education

Zespół Szkół i Placówek Oświatowych, Technikum nr 2, Nysa

I also obtained an IT Technician license



CERTIFICATE

2023 ISTQB Certified Tester Foundation Level

2018 Cisco IT Essentials



PRIVACY STATEMENT

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).